guys what the [ __ ] Hey guys do you
chavales qué [__] Oye chicos vosotros
think ibai got upset that the
creéis que a ibai le ha picado que el
other day I said that sometimes he throws stones
otro día dije que a veces tira la piedra
and hides his hand Well the same thing that
y esconde la mano Pues lo mismo que te
upset you when I released a video because
picó a ti cuando saqué un vídeo porque
you went to ibai's party
te fuiste a la velada de ibai
without a mask hugging
precisamente sin mascarilla abrazando a
the others and it turns out that later you tested
los demás y resulta que luego diste
positive for covid that you sent your
positivo en covid que mandaste a tu
agency to take the video And I
agencia a que me tirara el vídeo Y me
had to take a strike for three
tuve que comer un strike durante tres
months damn What the [ __ ] I just
meses [__] What the fuck acabo de
freaked out Hey he banned me from his channel
flipar Oye me ha baneado de su canal
guys for saying that when he doesn't
chicos por decir que que cuando no
want to say things he asks someone else the
quiere decir las cosas le hace a otro la
question that you can't stand each other that he can't
pregunta que no se soportan que no lo
stand it am I right and instead of
soporta estoy en lo cierto y en vez de
talking to me privately he
hablarlo conmigo por privado me me ha
banned me it's a joke no I can't stand you
baneado es coña no que no soportándoos
[Music]
[Música]